{
	"1": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Which of the following would the Java coding snippet return as its output?",
				"answers": ["0", "10", "1", "Compile time error"],
				"correct": 2
			}
		]
	},
	"2": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Which of the following combinations would the Java coding snippet print?",
				"answers": ["0 1", "1 0 ", "0 0", "null"],
				"correct": 2
			}
		]
	},
	"3": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "What would be the outcome of this Java coding snippet?",
				"answers": [
					"Welcome",
					"Welcome Welcome",
					"Type mismatch error",
					"Run infinite-times"
				],
				"correct": 2
			}
		]
	},
	"4": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "What's the outcome of this Java coding snippet?",
				"answers": [
					"Welcome",
					"None",
					"Type mismatch error",
					"Run infinite-times"
				],
				"correct": 0
			}
		]
	},
	"5": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Which of the following values would this Java coding snippet print in results?",
				"answers": ["0", "1", "2", "Compilation error"],
				"correct": 1
			}
		]
	},
	"6": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "What does this Java coding snippet print on execution?",
				"answers": ["Compilation fails.", "3", "2", "99"],
				"correct": 3
			}
		]
	},
	"7": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Which of the following values would this Java coding snippet yield?",
				"answers": ["199", "199.5", "200", "Invalid number"],
				"correct": 2
			}
		]
	},
	"8": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "What would this Java coding snippet return as its output?",
				"answers": [
					"An exception occurs while instantiating the A class.",
					"It'll print “This is a class A instance”",
					"The program will print null",
					"Compilation error at line number 13"
				],
				"correct": 1
			}
		]
	},
	"9": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "What would the this method yield when called?",
				"answers": [
					"If a and b both are true, then the output is “A && B”",
					"If a is true and b is false, then the output is “!B”",
					"If a is false and b is true, then the output is “None”",
					"If a and b both are false, then the output is “None”"
				],
				"correct": 2
			}
		]
	},
	"10": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "What will be the output of this Java coding snippet?",
				"answers": ["abc", "abcd", "abcde", "abcdef"],
				"correct": 0
			}
		]
	}
}
